{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Who is the current President of Nigeria?",
      "options": [
        "Asiwaju Bola Ahmed TInubu",
        "Olusegun Obasanjo",
        "Goodluck Jonathan",
        "Yemi Osinbajo"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the capital city of Nigeria?",
      "options": ["Lagos", "Abuja", "Kano", "Port Harcourt"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which state is the largest by area in Nigeria?",
      "options": ["Niger", "Borno", "Kogi", "Kaduna"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which year did Nigeria gain independence?",
      "options": ["1960", "1963", "1976", "1980"],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Nigeria's official currency?",
      "options": ["Dollar", "Cedi", "Naira", "Pound"],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Who was Nigeria's first president?",
      "options": [
        "Nnamdi Azikiwe",
        "Obafemi Awolowo",
        "Ahmadu Bello",
        "Yakubu Gowon"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which sector contributes the most to Nigeria's GDP?",
      "options": [
        "Agriculture",
        "Oil and Gas",
        "Telecommunications",
        "Banking and Finance"
      ],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "Which river is the longest in Nigeria?",
      "options": ["Niger River", "Benue River", "Gongola River", "Ogun River"],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "Which Nigerian state is known as the 'Food Basket of the Nation'?",
      "options": ["Lagos", "Kano", "Benue", "Kaduna"],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the current Governor of Lagos State?",
      "options": [
        "Akinwunmi Ambode",
        "Babatunde Fashola",
        "Jide Sanwo-Olu",
        "Dapo Abiodun"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "When was the Nigerian civil war?",
      "options": ["1967-1970", "1957-1960", "1977-1980", "1987-1990"],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "Which Nigerian city is known as the 'Center of Excellence'?",
      "options": ["Abuja", "Kano", "Ibadan", "Lagos"],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which Nigerian state has the highest population?",
      "options": ["Lagos", "Kano", "Kaduna", "Oyo"],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the current Minister of Health in Nigeria?",
      "options": [
        "Osagie Ehanire",
        "Isaac Adewole",
        "Chukwu Onyebuchi",
        "Emmanuel Ibe Kachikwu"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "When is Nigeria's Democracy Day celebrated?",
      "options": ["May 29", "June 12", "October 1", "January 1"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 20
    }
  ]
}
